let quiz = [
    {
        question: "Many teachers always  ____________ much homework.",
        option: [
            "Give",
            "Gives",
            "Are give",
            "Is give",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "They_________ look at me everyday",
        option: [
            "Does",
            "Doesn't",
            "Aren't",
            "Don't",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "_______ your grandparent let you go to bed late?",
        option: [
            "Are",
            "Does",
            "Is",
            "Do"
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question:
            "________ my father wait for you every affternoon?",
        option: [
            "Do",
            "Does",
            "Will",
            "Is",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question:
            "She_______ a movie everyday.",
        option: [
            "Watch",
            "Watches",
            "Watching",
            "Watchs",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "He doesn't _______ breakfast at my home.",
        option: ["Eats", "Eating", "Eat", "Ate"],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Does_____ love my cat?",
        option: [
            "She",
            "We",
            "I",
            "all firends",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Do ______ my father?",
        option: ["She hates", "You hate ", "My mother hating", "My friend love"],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "She ____ a book to my room?",
        option: ["Brings", "Bringing", "Bring", "Is bring"],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "They _____ to school?",
        option: ["Don't go", "Don't be going", "Doesn't go", "Is going"],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Kalimat (-) dari kalimat 'Dia membeli sayur di pasar' adalah",
        option: ["She don't buy vegetables in market", "She doesn't buy vegetables in market", "She is not buy vegetables in market", "She not buy vegetables in market"],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Kalimat (?) dari kalimat 'Dia membeli sayur di pasar' adalah",
        option: ["Do I buy vegetables in market?", "Does she buy vegetables in market?", "Do he buy vegetables in market?", "Does he buy vegetables in market?"],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Kalimat (+) dari kalimat 'Dia tidak membeli sayur di pasar' adalah",
        option: ["I buy vegetables in market", "She buy vegetables in market", "He buys vegetables in market", "She buys vegetables in market"],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Mereka membawaku ke rumahmu",
        option: ["They bring me to your house", "They brings me to your house", "They bringing me to your house", "They brought me to your house"],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Saya tidak meninggalkan mereka di sungai",
        option: ["She doesn't leave me in the river", "I doesn't leave me in the river", "I don't leave them in the river", "Me doesn't leave they in the river"],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Manakah kalimat yang benar di bawah ini",
        option: ["They look at I in my room", "I see their in a room", "They need me everyday", "Me love you"],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Manakah kalimat yang benar di bawah ini",
        option: ["Theirs house looks messy", "Theirs is mine", "Mine is your", "Them I love their room"],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Manakah kalimat yang benar di bawah ini",
        option: ["Their room is so small", "They doesn't like me", "Paijo don't bring me a flower", "I love wearing a cloth"],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Manakah kalimat yang benar di bawah ini",
        option: ["Do she look good?", "Do you lovers me?", "Does she type in my computer?", "Does my grandparents die?"],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Manakah kalimat yang benar di bawah ini",
        option: ["I don't links it to my friend?", "It doesn't suit me", "Does she brings in my computer?", "Do my grandparents dies at hotel?"],
        answer: 1,
    },
];

